# **Shrujan Shetty**

A passionate Front-End engineer with over 10 years of experience in Vanilla Javascript, typescript, and JS frameworks like Angular and React. Proficient in object-oriented design development with good problem-solving skills and experience in Agile methodology.

Panaji Goa. India 7204347725 shrork@gmail.com

#### **EXPERIENCE**

### Persistent Systems, Goa, Remote

April 2018 - PRESENT

- Built multiple products for multiple clients in Angular and React.
- Led a team of 4 Front end developers to <u>build 3 rich analytical</u> <u>features from scratch and received appreciation from the client's</u> <u>Director.</u>
- Built an application that scans user's cloud accounts to identify problems with them according to GDPR and HIPAA standards.
- <u>Built a rich Admin Portal from scratch</u> to aid onboarding and customer tracking.
- Built an Application to direct the user to the nearby dispensary.
- Coordinated with the UX team and developed Ul templates using web technologies like Flexbox, and Grids to develop a dashboard optimized even for Mobile devices.
- <u>Coordinated with multiple remote teams</u> spread across different time zones.
- Optimized existing code base to improve the performance and usability of the application.
- Committed the code to GitLab, GitHub daily
- Work includes Sync with Product and API teams, Code review,
   Performance optimization & ensuring smooth releases.

# Techjini Solutions (DataMatics), Bangalore

July 2012 - March 2018

- Began my career by working in a startup company where I implemented multiple projects using Vanilla JavaScript and JavaScript-based frameworks like Angular JS.
- Developed a responsive web application using web technologies like HTML, CSS, and PHP to keep track of employees and the leaves taken by them.
- Collaborated with a large team to design a portal where the customers can view their advertisements, and manage, track, optimize, and measure campaigns across brands and <u>received an</u> <u>award from the CTO for my work</u>.
- Implemented the Front-end Web Design of the portal using

#### **SKILLS**

Data structures and problem-solving, JavaScript, HTML, CSS, SCSS, Angular, React, JSON, GIT, GitLab, Agile, JIRA, Rest API and Agile Methodologies

#### **AWARDS**

High Five - Individual Award (2024)

High Five - Team Award (2023)

Bravo Team Award (2022)

Received multiple client appreciations. (2021-22)

Superior Customer Service Award (2017)

Beyond the Call of Duty (2014)

#### **LANGUAGES**

English, Hindi, Konkani, and Tulu

#### **EDUCATION**

AIMIT, Mangalore — MCA

Vanilla JavaScript, HTML, and CSS promoting a brand through a movie for kids.

2009 - 2012

Don Bosco College, Panaji—

2006 - 2009

#### **SOME PROJECTS**

# Firewalker, LionLeaf — Personal Dispensary Locator

Tools and Technologies used: React, NextJS

Firewalker provides the public with easy directions to nearby dispensaries, highlights popular products, and recommends new trending items. Meanwhile, it also offers store owners insights into the latest trends and customer preferences, enabling them to make better decisions.

# **Remedy Engine, ClearData** — Cloud catalyst. Healthcare protector

Tools and Technologies used: Angular, Typescript, GraphQL, ChartJS, GoLang Remedy Engine offers one of the best solutions to the healthcare industry to protect their patient's information. By adopting modern cloud technologies, healthcare organizations can be sure that sensitive data is private, secure, and compliant.

## **Visto** — Digital Advertising Platform

Tools and Technologies used: Angular, Typescript, ChartJS

Visto is a digital advertising platform used by Agencies and Media

Companies. It provides a platform-agnostic ad hub with a single interface
to manage, track, optimize and measure campaigns across brands,
products, regions, and agencies and also provides reports.

# **Bumble Bee Seafoods** — Hero Of Color City

Tools and Technologies used: Vanilla JS, HTML, CSS

This project was developed to promote the film named HOCC (Hero Of Color City). This is a web application through which kids can play a few games and adults can learn to prepare tasty recipes.

#### **Boston Marathon World Run** — *Virtual Marathon*

Tools and Technologies used: Vanilla JS, HTML, CSS

A virtual marathon to raise money for the victims of the 2014 Boston bombing. Here the participants can click and upload pictures of themselves and upload them to the site. Users can also view the pictures in the gallery.